<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BMU APP</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_screen">MainScreen</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="aboutus1">Founded by The Hero Group, BML Munjal University (BMU) is a not-for-profit initiative offering undergraduate and post-graduate courses in management (MBA and BBA) and undergraduate courses in engineering (BTech) and commerce (BCom (Hons)). The University has been founded with the objective of transforming higher education in India by creating a world-class teaching and learning environment. The 50-acre, fully residential and co-educational university has been notified under the Haryana State Private Universities Act, 2006.</string>
    <string name="aboutus2">Named after the chairman and founder of the Hero Group, Brijmohan Lall Munjal, BMU is engaged in creating, preserving and imparting internationally benchmarked knowledge and skills to a diverse community of students from across the world. The Hero Group is a US$ 5 billion group which includes Hero MotoCorp – the world’s largest two-wheeler manufacturer.</string>
    <string name="aboutus3">BMU is mentored by Imperial College London, the 108-year old University that is currently ranked 9th in the QS World University rankings (2016-2017).</string>
    <string name="aboutus4">The campus is located at the 67th KM stone on NH-8, District Gurgaon, Haryana, about 50 km from New Delhi International Airport.</string>
    <string name="mastechef1">Masterchef 2017 is the flagship event of 67th mlestone our very ow technical cultural and managemnt fest . In this 16 teams including our bmu team participated . and we have 3 rounds  </string>
    <string name="masterchefabout">MasterChef is the pinnacle form of Gourmet competition held in recent years. Here, at BML Munjal University, we try to emulate and assimilate all the various types of aspects of art and culture in our road to development and Progress."\n" "\n" This was an inter college event where teams would compete with each other to prove their skills and talents in to find out who’s dominant in world of cuisine. On 3 rd of March 2017, the competition MasterChef was set in motion. After Judges sharing their experience with the 8 teams , there was Round 1 that was a quiz based on cooking arena. It was an intellectual and mind focusing competition.All teams with great knowledge and wisdom bravely faced the questions and answered them accurately .With such force and improvisation, around 7 teams qualified for Round 2.</string>
    <string name="winnermch1"> 1st - BHM, Amity University,Noida "\n" 2nd - BML Munjal University "\n" 3rd - Eco kart team from Kerala</string>
    <string name="prizemasterchef">1st prize - 10,000 voucher from Sodexo + gift hamper &amp; certificate from BMU Culinary Club + certificates from university and Compass group."\n" "\n" 2nd prize - 7,000 voucher from Sodexo + certificates from BMU Culinary Club and Compass group. "\n" "\n" 3rd prize - 5,000 voucher from Sodexo + certificates from BMU Culinary Club &amp; Compass group.</string>
    <string name="sodexo_breakfast">------------------------------"\n" Milk "\n" Coffee "\n" Tea "\n" Cornflakes "\n" Parantha</string>
    <string name="sodexo_lunch">------------------------------"\n" Yellow dal"\n" Soya Chap "\n" Arbi Masala "\n" Raita "\n" Roti</string>


    <string name="dip">At the end of the course the students should be able to understand the fundamentals behind formation - capturing of images, processing and analyzing digital images. They will be able to understand the concept of image compression and multi-resolution images. They will have an understanding of where digital images are used in real-life applications and they will be able to apply their knowledge in implementing programs involving digital image processing.</string>
    <string name="cc">This course is designed for Third Year Engineering students. The aim of the course is to set students at the forefront of understanding on Cloud Computing Technology and to help them build their skills to develop large-scale industry standard applications using cloud platforms and tools. With this course, students can gain a solid knowledge of cloud computing and the framework for using this knowledge in diverse applications.</string>
    <string name="mbsd">Knowledge of the structure, organization, operation and interconnection of computerized systems, the basics of programming, and its application for solving problems of engineering.</string>
    <string name="ds">The course aims at making students aware of different types of distributed systems and their trends, as well as an understanding of the principles, techniques, challenges and practices in the design and implementation of distributed systems. The course discusses in details various communication protocols and algorithms required to implement distributed systems.</string>
    <string name="ied">·Helping students examine their entrepreneurial attributes and innovation insight.

·The major emphasis of the course will be on creating a learning system through which students can acquaint themselves with the special challenges of starting new ventures and introducing new product and service ideas.

·Help students review large number of successful cases bring learning insight and develop marketable business plan.</string>
    <string name="iot"> The aim of this course "Internet of Things (IoT)” is to practically visualise real world problems, analyse it and then design the solution for that problem using smart components such as sensors.  </string>


    <string name="attendance_grade_33_39">Attendance Grade : 33/39</string>
    <string name="grade_84_62">Grade : 84.62%</string>
    <string name="absent_6">Absent : 6</string>
    <string name="present_33">Present : 33</string>
    <string name="sessions_completed_39">Sessions Completed : 39</string>
    <string name="subject_digital_image_processing">SUBJECT: DIGITAL IMAGE PROCESSING</string>


</resources>
